

Sherkhan **Tulkibay**



DESIRED POSITION

Frontent developer

ABOUT

Front-end developer with experience:

- creating a SPA using React JS and Redux;
- creating static websites using Gatsby JS and Strapi.

I have knowledge in the field of user interface, testing and debugging. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with the help of new technologies.

Capable of effective self-management, as well as team collaboration.

Open for your suggestions



EDUCATION

ENU (Master's degree)

2016-2018

"Space technique and technology"

KazATU (Bachelor's degree)

2010-2014

"Radiotechnic, electronic and telecommunications"



WORK EXPERIENCE

State Technical Service JSC

Front-end developer

06.2021-Present

- layout interfaces according to the layout, write new functionality, maintain and develop the design system. Project stack (Laravel, PostgreSQL, JS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)

Department of information and commincation MIA RK 07.2015-06.2021 Senior engineer

- technical support of video conferencing
- technical support for local network and telephony
- development of technical specifications
- perform official duties in a timely and high-quality manner documents

Technical support center of ENU Engineer

11.2014-07.2015

- technical support for local network and telephony
- current repair of computer equipment
- installation and maintenance of university buildings software solutions

PORTFOLIO

Attps://sherkhan61.github.io/portfolio-2/



CONTACTS



+7 777 774 1361



🕅 sherkhan-92@bk.ru



Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan



linkedin.com/in/sherkhan-tulkibay



https://github.com/sherkhan61



t.me/sherkhan61



ADDITIONALLY

My motto

Follow your DREAMS and the Universe will open doors FOR YOU where there were ONLY WALLS



LANGUAGES

English: A2



SKILLS

- + JavaScript
- + TypeScript
- + React JS
- + Gatsby JS
- + Strapi
- + HTML5
- + CSS3
- + SCSS
- + Flexbox

- + Redux
 - + Axios
 - + GraphQL
 - + Bootstrap
- + Material UI
- + Formik
- + Git